(Sheldon:)upon meeting this colonel?
(Penny:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Am I allowed to inform him
(Sheldon:)that Colonel Sanders was never
actually in the military?
(Leonard:)I'm getting enraged.
(Raj:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Ooh.
(Sheldon:)Can I use text-to-speech
software?
No!
(Leonard:)Don't speak.
(Sheldon's phone:)Aw, nuts.
Gentlemen!
(Colonel Williams:)I'm Colonel
Williams.
(Colonel Williams:)Thank you for meeting with me.
(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Hello.
(Colonel Williams:)So, which one of you is
the brains behind all this?
(Howard:)It's a group effort,
(Howard:)but I guess if we had to pick
a main brain, it would be me.
(Colonel Williams:)And because
of the quantum vortices,
(Colonel Williams:)this can run perpetually?
(Leonard:)Exactly.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you have a good
grasp of the physics.
(Colonel Williams:)Well, I'm a scientist
by training.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Howard:)You're a physicist?
(Colonel Williams:)Better. I'm an engineer.